All right. Hello, everyone,
and welcome to the
CS6300 Subway Development
Process Office Hour.
My name is Shin, and
with me is Tara and Will.
Hello, everyone.
Hi, everyone.
All right. So this is the
first office hour after our
two-week break. So the
week before, it was meeting
assignment six. So it was
during communication lockdown.
And last week was
the spring break,
well, at least spring
break in Georgia.
I just made aware that
spring break is not
the same week for the
whole United States.
Oh, it's not even the
same in all Georgia.
Okay.
No, but that's the official
spring break week for
this year. for georgia tech
so that's why we picked
this is what i'm saying
university as their own
sometimes overlap and
clearly doesn't overlap
with kids with kids spring
break that is different
by county so yeah oh yeah
new hampshire is weird
because we have a tab
because we have so much snow
uh they have a tendency to have
uh the break a little bit later
um so ours is different than
most states for some reason
so there is maybe there
is at least one flower
somewhere exactly anyway anyway
um not what people are here
to hear so let's see for the
schedule this week students
are supposed to watch
p4l4 i share development
methods lecture and been
working on individual projects,
deliverable one, so APD1,
and we already closed,
supposedly closed ASICs
last week during Spring
Break, well, no, the
week before, however,
there are some accommodation
that the students will
some students are still
working on that now
so that is the reason we
not do the live solution
walkthrough of ASICS
today but it is our plan
to have a six solution
book through next
week because i think
it is the the last case
of accommodation and we
expect the submission
very soon and a
blue project rate is
more as ready it needs my
final uh verification and i
will push and students have
uh first two weeks for any
grade request for a sixth
grade we will release it um
during during next wednesday
so we probably before
probably or maybe after but
definitely be during the
day that we have the solution
because it is for any
students who want to make
a request on assignment
six it is explicitly
required for the students to
acknowledge that they have
watched the whole solution
and understand it before
making the request it's
a standard to reduce any
so called false positive or
noisy requests just because
that hey can you look
at my submission well we
cannot just give a blanket
regret as you don't have
to specifically point out
what they think is
an erroneous trading
decision okay so with
that i think we can
go to the OH question for now.
You have just
muted yourself, so
now they're not
hearing you anymore.
**** it.
I was saying, first of
all, happy April phones.
It was the first comment
on the OH thread.
Yeah, I already
explained the reason
we skipped the data source OH.
As for the next
students questions this is
a true practice is there
an expected or approximate
number of lines in
our cut part to ensure we
have sufficient coverage
and just didn't already
answer yeah we don't have
any uh well i mean um
students can do as long
as car props, but our IPD1
requirements specifically
have the link number,
I think it's 50 to 90
test cases. So the
longer you write
the car property,
the less likely you
will contain within
maximum test cases.
But also, I mean, make sure
you're using it properly
because Because people
don't always, sometimes
people sort of try and
shortchange around what it's
supposed to do for you,
and that will not do very
well for your grading. If
you try and brute force
things that the tool is
supposed to be doing for
you, that will probably
harm your grade quite a bit.
um and see solution yeah
okay and uh the second
question is already
i'm just in already
answer that is i also
just need to reiterate
that is true that there
is no one right answer
on the other hand
there are definitely
wrong wrong solution
as well so usually
students get deducted
for wrong solution
not that they not that
they don't have the
single resolution
that the operator is
looking at we do have
rubric so we do have
the the list of the
the laundry list of
okay does the solution
have this aspect
or consider this
edge case, et cetera,
but yeah, we don't have
a single solution. It's
the same thing, the rubric
itself is composable,
just like the test
cases as well, so
we compose multiple
angles, and each
of them has specific
weight to that.
Yeah, there are several
correct ways, there
are several ways to do
it correctly, but there
are also several ways
to do it incorrectly.
Okay. And that's all the
questions for now. So
what topic should the
podcast today talk about?
Well,
can we, we have to do
something to keep Paola awake.
well
for sure
recently well I just
followed the news and
flow code just leaked
the whole code base
in there and somebody
was saying that is
ironically that the company
who say oh yeah developer
is going to lose the job
within six months now has
the AI slot of just linking
the whole artifact online
okay see
we're just waiting to
see if anybody asks
more questions is that
what we're doing here
yep um try to get more
okay so um will what's
your favorite um a west
operation system to
work with let's say in
in your personal daily
life or with uh when
you are working um i'm a
big fan i think that
there's our three choices,
right? There's Linux.
I'm a big fan of Linux.
In point of fact, because
most of what I'm doing
nowadays isn't development,
nowadays is just a user.
I tend to mostly use
Windows because a lot of
stuff is not necessarily
built for Linux, and it
doesn't run properly on
Linux, and it's a pain
to install it on Linux.
So So I tend to run
Windows and then I have the
Windows or Linux subsystem
on Windows or whatever
it's called installed so
I can sort of do both.
So all of my grading
and stuff I try and
do in Linux because
I like that better.
But when I'm just browsing
and playing games and
that sort of stuff, most
of that's on Windows.
What about you?
the reason i'm asking because
you don't have to keep
me out and be worried about
me i can also answer but
it's gonna be an awful answer
because i'm the average
person have you ever heard
about this study on people and
usability that even if you
are unhappy with something
when you get used to it it's
very difficult to change
so at some point of my life
they gave me a mac and i
cannot get out of it so now
all my life is on that i'm
the average user so i got
something even when i'm not
fully satisfied i stay there
yeah well i mean not getting
out of mac is a lot of
windows user experience as
well that's that's what i
heard so they decided there's
a windows and then sometimes
actually that that's my
my story i actually have i
was a windows user when i
was a student and then during
the student time undergraduate
student time i tried
hacking those you know like
running mac os on uh the mac
hardware and then i spent
like two months doing the
hacking those and at some
point i just like mac os and
the way it is working and
then i pay premium just to
get the the MacBook so that
I don't have to hack it all
the way to hack in those.
Just so you know, there
are some more questions.
Thanks for keeping that.
There is one student
asked piggyback questions.
What's an example of
the wrong way? I saw
the calculator example
and seems to be along
the lines of don't
change the function.
So the example of the wrong
way, either you should be
able to think or manifest
yourself, or you have to
wait, or you have to make a
mistake and get the points
deducted for that. Because
if we are making any example
for this specific assignment,
then it is already
regretting, which could be
unfair for all the students. Just
remember what the tool is
supposed to do for you and
make sure you're using it
the way it should be done.
And if you look at the
output from it and you start
going, hey, this isn't
really generating. uh i
mean the the worst mistake
that i one of the worst
mistakes i see and this
is general enough that i
think we can say it is
being so generic with your
various different partitions
and stuff that it doesn't
that the the generated
test frames don't actually
lead themselves to anything
specific right and if
you do something like
that and there's no way to
verify that any test frame
that you write really
matches the test frame that
was generated or test case
that you write matches
the generated test frame,
you won't get points
for it. Because if you
can't be wrong, if you
can't be right, then you
can't be wrong, right?
So make sure it is
specific enough that a test
frame very specifically
tells you what your
test is supposed to be.
I think that's fair, right?
Cool. Okay,
the next question.
Thank you. If you
can give some advice
on how not to overthink
the assignment.
How to not overthink
this assignment.
Will, I think it's on
the same thought chain.
Do you have any advice?
I think kind of what
we just did is, is
sort of it, you
know, it's, it's, um,
I mean, it's, it's,
it's not rocket science.
The tool is not
anything other than,
you know, what it is. It's,
it's, there's no, there's
no hidden thing behind
it. There's not something
that you're, oh, let's
see who's smart enough to
find the little, you know,
Easter egg or something in
it. It's, it's a
straightforward tool, but just
make sure you're using it
the way it should be used.
okay next question in
part two can i import
library slide share unit
in my main test server
um you can test it yourself
again um just to spend
the answer if grayscope
allow you to do so then yes
you can do so um in the
past there were some kind of
stress test or ***********
for the student that did
not follow the instructor
intention for which we
applauded the students and
give them some extra points.
So, but in general,
we already hardened
the Grayscope, so if
it allows you to import
and run it, then
yeah, just go for it.
also for also for part two
next question uh do we need
manually write test case
or do we need a tool in
part one we yeah so in part
two uh you would manually
write a test case based
on the generated frame um
again manually right here
means manually right not even
ai assisted uh yeah test
writing because it is the
cross syllabus um if we
are going to update that
syllabus in the future that
would be the future semester
not this one um i i acknowledge
that in the industry
right now um it is likely
that if you um if you have
such test frame generated
it's more or less trivial
to collect uh letter ai to
help you write those test
cases again that is not
acceptable in this course but
you might find it in the
industry however just uh
unsolicited advice if you are
doing that in the industry
make sure that at least
you read it afterwards you
read the the general test
cases afterwards just like
um the being the because
the ta um in this case will
also read your test frame
and the uh the written test
case make sure the test
frames match the test case
semantics yep and and and
that by the way is another
thing every semester there's
at least a couple of people
that think they're going
to be really, really smart
and write a parser that
parses the results and
automatically runs the test
frame. So each test frame is
just run frame one, run
frame two, run frame three,
and then the thing parses
it and runs everything. And
that's really slick and it's
really cool and you don't
get any points for it
because you didn't write the
tests. So just be aware
of that. If you try and do
that, that's a lot of work
you're going to do. And in
the real world, that might
work really well. But for
the purpose of this assignment,
that will not get you
points and you will not be
happy with the result. So
do not do that. Write them
manually. I know it's a
pain writing 50 to 90 tests,
but write them manually.
You know, I mean,
there's a fair amount of
cut and pasting you can
do for most of them,
you know, and just change
arguments and change
inputs and change outputs
and that sort of thing.
So it shouldn't be as
hard as writing, you
know, 50 to 90 completely
separate tests,
but write them yourself,
write them specifically,
because if you have
anything that parses
and generates, you won't
get points for that.
Which is too bad, because
it's really kind of
a slick solution when
people do it. It's just
not what this assignment's
supposed to be about.
OK, I think we went
through all the questions.
Oh,
yeah. That's right.
Do the test frames a
body or a skeleton?
The test frames or the tests?
The test frames.
Because the test frames
are what are generated in
your TSL output file.
The test cases are what
you write from the test
frames. The test cases need
a body. The test cases
you are implementing,
the test frames that
were generated, you are
implementing into test cases
in your output. I think
that's the question you're
asking. I'm not sure.
That's what I
asked him as well.
Yeah. So if you needed
something different
than that, please
write a follow-up real
quickly and we'll
vamp for a little bit.
Yes, thanks.
Okay, good.
Anyway, back to you
were saying we've done
them all and then
another one came in.
What was that?
You were just saying, okay,
so I guess we've answered
all the questions and then
another one came in. So do
you want to go back to that
now? I mean, yeah, if we
are already finished, then
we can just call it a day.
But yeah,
call it a night, call
it a day, depends
on part of the world
that you are at.
But yeah, if there's
nothing, then I
think just, is it
Easter this weekend?
Is this weekend what? Easter?
Yeah.
It's this weekend, yes.
Okay.
Then, I mean, yeah.
Happy Easter, everyone,
especially those
with children within
the egg hunting ages.
Yeah.
Good luck with eggs
you're going to never find
again and are going to
melt in your backyard.
And, by the way, just a quick
complaint about consumerism
in the U.S. I'm fine with
the egg hunting, but I
am not fine with the egg
having too much sugar in it,
and I always have to, like,
okay, and by the way, also
shout out to certain
organizations and churches with
the egg hunting, not having
candy or sugars, but more
like toothpaste or some
veggie snack, so that is
something that I really want
to just point out randomly.
and you can tell you can
see the difference between
uh shin's body weight and
mine that i'm not going to
agree with any of that i
love the candy way too much
but that's i love that
part of things i think a
compromise between you know
the too many candies and veggie
snacks could be stickers
i'm just saying i'm trying
you know to make parents
and kids happy at the same
time but i just wanted to
say these things the veggie
snack remind me of something
i really wanted to do
for my kids for the first
of april uh for april full
i saw this and i didn't
have time today i wanted to
create you know those i
don't know they're called
they look like lollipops
but they really like small
cakes yeah so i wanted to do
them but instead of putting
a cake inside putting
the brussels sprouts so i
wanted to cover but i didn't
have time so i arrived too
late to do it i thought
that would have been great
i'm giving you the idea for
next year now if easter was
actually on april fool's
day that would be perfect
or or like the the you
know more extreme veggies
next little brussels sprouts
and cook brussels browser
yes all right well it does
not look like we've got
any more so yep all right
um so let's um yeah finish
it then thank you everyone
and see you next week
see you next week everyone
next week Happy Easter